world-nuclear-news.org 2019-12-02

# Privacy Notice - World Nuclear News

World Nuclear Association, registered in England and Wales, number 01215741.  
Registered office: Tower House, 10 Southampton Street, London, WC2E 7HA, United Kingdom

  Our websites: [www.world-nuclear.org](http://www.world-nuclear.org/), [www.world-nuclear-news.org](http://www.world-nuclear-news.org/), [www.world-nuclear-university.org](http://www.world-nuclear-university.org/),  [www.wna-symposium.org](http://www.wna-symposium.org/),  [members.world-nuclear.org](http://members.world-nuclear.org/)

This policy provides you with information about:

\- Information collected by us

\- Use of your information

\- Personal data security

\- Correction/Updating/Deletion of personal information 

\- Marketing

\- General

\- Governing law

\- Contact details

**Information collected by us**  
The Association collects information about website visitors and subscribers during their registration for corporate events, workshops and seminars, or any other event hosted by The Association. This information may include: name, address, email address, contact telephone number, date of birth and passport details (where visas are required). The Association may also collect personal data of the same nature for any accompanying persons. The Association may also collect information where visitors or subscribers participate in certain Association activities, such as questionnaires and surveys, and through the use of cookies. When visitors request pages from our server, our web server automatically collects some information about them, including their IP addresses. These addresses are used by computers on the network to send the requested pages to visitors.

By using this website and providing your personal data to The Association you understand and agree that The Association and its affiliates may: a) use your personal data; and b) share your personal data with third parties, both as described below.

**Use of your information  **  
The Association may collect, use and store your personal data, as described in this Privacy Policy, where necessary in order to:

(a) perform any contract to which you are party (such as providing you with services) or in order to take steps at your request prior to entering into such a contract;

(b) exercise our legitimate business interests, for example where you have signed up for any of our events, by sharing your name, company and email address with other delegates to that event via our password-protected event website and publishing the details in the event programme;

(c) carry out other functions with your specific consent, such as providing you with information e.g. via our website;

(d) ensure that the website is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;

(e) in accordance with our legitimate business interests and legal obligations.

The Association will not reveal any of your personal information to any third party without your permission or as permitted in accordance with our legitimate interests or as required by law. The Association uses visitors’ IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer the website. We also use it to gather broad demographic information about our visitors in general. This information does not contain any details that can identify visitors personally.

Using email addresses and appropriate indications of consent provided at registration or collected otherwise, The Association periodically sends out email newsletters and promotional emails to our visitors about services and publications offered by this website. Visitors can indicate whether they wish to receive such information from The Association and may update their preferences by following the instructions included in each such communication. Third parties will not contact our website visitors through the use of our email lists.

This website uses cookies to deliver content specific to visitors’ interests and to respect their preferences. This information is used to assist us in creating a site that will serve the needs of our visitors. Please note that if you decline to accept cookies, you may be required to register each time you wish to download materials from the website. For information on cookies and how we use them see our Cookie Policy.

The Association will only process your personal data to the extent that it is necessary for the purposes specified in this Privacy Policy and will not keep your personal data for longer than is necessary for such purposes.

Given the global nature of The Association and its business, we may need to transfer your information to countries outside of the European Economic Area in order to provide our services to you. Where this is necessary, The Association will ensure that the appropriate safeguards are in place in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and also the Data Protection Act (2018).

**Personal data security**  
The Association maintains appropriate technical and organisational security measures to protect your personal information from theft, loss, misuse, and against unauthorised access, disclosure, alteration or destruction.

**Correction/Updating/Deletion of personal information  **  
You have the right to access your personal information and to require the correction and updating, of inaccurate and/or incorrect data. In addition to this right, you also have the right to:

  * Restrict or object to how The Association or its third parties or affiliates process your data;
  * be provided with information about how your personal data is processed (this information is set out in this Privacy Policy);
  * have your personal data erased in certain circumstances;
  * have your personal data transferred to yourself or to another data controller;  
     and 
  * not to be subject to automated decision making, including profiling.

If your personal information changes, or you want to exercise any of these rights, or you have any other comments, questions or complaints about your personal data, please notify [dpo@world-nuclear.org](mailto:dpo@world-nuclear.org)

You also have the right to take any complaints about how we process your personal data to the Information Commissioner:

Information Commissioner’s Office, Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, Cheshire SK9 5AF

<https://ico.org.uk/concerns/>  0303 123 1113.

**Marketing**

Photography and videoing may take place at events organized by the Association. Images and video material are owned by World Nuclear Association and may be used in press releases, printed publicity, on our website and/or on our social media channels. If you would like to see your images and/or film, or would like us to delete them, please email us at [dpo@world-nuclear.org](mailto:dpo@world-nuclear.org) at any time. 

**General  **

The Association is not responsible for the content, cookies or the privacy policies of websites to which it may provide links. The Association reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy from time to time without prior notice – please check regularly for any amendments (but NB amendments will not be made retrospectively).

**Governing law**  
This website is governed by and shall be construed in accordance with English law and any dispute as to its terms shall be submitted to the exclusive jurisdiction of the English courts.

**Contact us  **  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement or the practices of this website you can contact us at [dpo@world-nuclear.org](mailto:dpo@world-nuclear.org) or by writing to the Data Protection Officer, World Nuclear Association, Tower House, 10 Southampton Street, London, WC2E 7HA, United Kingdom.

* * *
